[
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of South Korea?",
        "choices": [
            "Pyongyang",
            "Seoul",
            "Busan",
            "Jeju"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the South Korean typical attire called?",
        "choices": [
            "Hanbok",
            "Yukata",
            "Kimono",
            "Suit"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a jimjilbang?",
        "choices": [
            "A one-room mixed hostel",
            "A bath house",
            "A purification ceremony",
            "A Cafe"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the Boseong tea plantations known for?",
        "choices": [
            "Black Tea",
            "White Tea",
            "Grenn tea",
            "Coffee"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a hanok?",
        "choices": [
            "A private neighbourhood",
            "A palace",
            "A temple",
            "A traditional wooden house"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional sport in Korea?",
        "choices": [
            "Taekwondo",
            "Tennis",
            "Baseball",
            "Karate"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Korean city hosted the Asian Games in 2002?",
        "choices": [
            "Seoul",
            "Seogwipo",
            "Busan",
            "Ulsan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Korean word for the South Korean national flag?",
        "choices": [
            "Chunggukki",
            "Taegukki",
            "Minjuki",
            "Keungukki"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the population of South Korea?",
        "choices": [
            "48 million",
            "51 million",
            "57 million",
            "45million"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "South Korea has some popular spots for hikers. Which South Korean mountain is the highest?",
        "choices": [
            "Chiri-san",
            "Bukhansan",
            "Hallasan",
            "Seoraksan"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    }
]